<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<labels xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
 xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../labels.xsd" xmlns:gco="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gco"
 xmlns:gmd="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gmd" xmlns:srv="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/srv"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml" xmlns:gts="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gts"
 xmlns:gmx="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gmx">

 <!-- Based on https://taskman.eionet.europa.eu/Help/wiki/catalogue/metadata_guidelines -->

 <element name="gmd:code" id="207.0"
  context="gmd:MD_Metadata/gmd:referenceSystemInfo/gmd:MD_ReferenceSystem/gmd:referenceSystemIdentifier/gmd:RS_Identifier/gmd:code">
  <label>Unique resource identifier</label>
  <description>Alphanumeric value identifying an instance in the namespace.</description>
  <help><![CDATA[
   The Coordinate Reference System shall be referred to with its EPSG code 
   (<a href="http://www.spatialreference.org/">the spatial reference website</a> provides 
   a search interface to the EPSG database). When there is not any EPSG code to describe a CRS, 
   the CRS shall be described in the metadata. Contact Paul Hasenohr for further details.]]>
   </help>
  <condition>mandatory</condition>
  <helper>
   <option value="urn:ogc:def:crs:EPSG:7.1:3035"
    title="Lambert Azimuthal Equal Area 52N 10E projection based on ETRS89 datum">Lambert Azimuthal
    Equal Area (EPSG 3035)</option>
   <!-- TODO : add other standard projections -->
  </helper>
 </element>
 <element name="gmd:codeSpace" id="208.1">
  <label>Codespace</label>
  <description>Name or identifier of the person or organization responsible for
   namespace</description>
  <helper>
   <option value="OGP Surveying &amp; Positioning Committee">OGP Surveying &amp; Positioning
    Committee</option>
  </helper>
 </element>
 <element name="gmd:title" id="360.0"
  context="gmd:MD_Metadata/gmd:identificationInfo/gmd:MD_DataIdentification/gmd:citation/gmd:CI_Citation/gmd:title">
  <label>Title</label>
  <description>Name by which the cited resource is known</description>
  <condition>mandatory</condition>
  <help>
   <![CDATA[The title should be self-explanatory and should not contain acronyms unless they are widely known. 
   In any case, should an acronym be used in the title, it shall be made explicit in the abstract.
   For datasets with versions (directory name containing the dataset ending with _revXX), 
   the version number and the dataset creation date shall be added at the end of the title, 
   separated from the title with a space followed with an hyphen and a space as shown in 
   the example (Corine Land Cover 1990 - 2000 changes - <b>version 13, Feb. 2010</b>)]]>
  </help>
 </element>


 <element name="gmd:date" id="570.0"
  context="gmd:MD_Metadata/gmd:identificationInfo/gmd:MD_DataIdentification/gmd:citation/gmd:CI_Citation/gmd:date/gmd:CI_Date/gmd:date">
  <label>Date</label>
  <description>Reference date for the cited resource (YYYY-MM-DD)</description>
  <condition>mandatory</condition>
  <help>
   <![CDATA[The <b>date of publication</b> shall only be present for datasets which are already published on the EEA website.
  For datasets which are not published on the EEA website, this metadata element shall be removed.<br/>
  The date of creation shall be equal to the date of publication for datasets which are already published on the EEA website.
  <br/>
  The <b>date of creation</b> shall be equal to the date of publication for datasets which are already published on the EEA website.
  
  For datasets which are not published on the EEA website, this date might be retrieved from the metadata file generated 
  by the EEA metadata editor which could be available together with the dataset. If no suitable creation date can be found, 
  it shall default to 1950-06-01.
  ]]>
  </help>
 </element>


 <element name="gmd:edition" id="363.0"
  context="gmd:MD_Metadata/gmd:identificationInfo/gmd:MD_DataIdentification/gmd:citation/gmd:CI_Citation/gmd:edition">
  <label>Edition</label>
  <description>Version of the cited resource</description>
  <help><![CDATA[
   If the dataset has a revision number (such as the Corine Land Cover changes 1990-2000 version 13), 
   this revision number shall be written in this metadata element.
   ]]></help>
 </element>


 <element name="gmd:code" id="207.0"
  context="gmd:MD_Metadata/gmd:identificationInfo/gmd:MD_DataIdentification/gmd:citation/gmd:CI_Citation/gmd:identifier/gmd:RS_Identifier/gmd:code">
  <label>Unique resource identifier</label>
  <description>Alphanumeric value identifying an instance in the namespace.</description>
  <help><![CDATA[
   This identifier shall be unique and ideally meaningful.
   This identifier shall be set to the directory name (written according to 
   <a href="https://taskman.eionet.europa.eu/Help/wiki/ds/fbs_ref_dataset_l4">this convention</a>) 
   in which the dataset is contained.]]>
  </help>
 </element>

 <element name="gmd:abstract" id="25.0">
  <label>Abstract</label>
  <description>Brief narrative summary of the content of the resource(s)</description>
  <condition>mandatory</condition>
  <help><![CDATA[When the text is imported from a previous metadata record or from the EEA website, 
   the dataset name in the abstract (if present) might need some editing.
 Acronyms should be written in full when first used.]]></help>
 </element>


 <element name="gmd:pointOfContact" id="29.0" context="gmd:MD_DataIdentification">
  <label>Point of contact</label>
  <description>Identification of, and means of communication with, person(s) and
   organizations(s) associated with the resource(s)</description>
  <help><![CDATA[
    <h2>Point of contact</h2>
   The responsible party acting as Point of Contact is the EEA Information 
   Centre for any dataset owned by EEA.
   The responsible party acting as Point of Contact is the organization or company owning 
   the dataset when the latter is not owned by EEA.<br/>
   <h2>Custodian</h2>
   This metadata element applies only to datasets owned by EEA.<br/>
   <ul>
    <li>The custodian should be the Data Centre responsible for the resource. 
    In cases where there is not any responsible data centre, enter a default value of Other.</li>
    <li>The metadata element positionName/characterString shall be edited accordingly and take one of these values:
     <ul>
      <li>European air pollution data centre</li>
      <li>European biodiversity data centre</li>
      <li>European climate change data centre</li>
      <li>Environmental data centre for land use</li>
      <li>European water data centre</li>
      <li>Other</li>
     </ul>
    </li>
   </ul>
   ]]></help>
 </element>

 <element name="gmd:contact" id="29.0" context="gmd:MD_Metadata">
  <label>Point of contact</label>
  <description>Identification of, and means of communication with, person(s) and
   organizations(s) associated with the resource(s)</description>
  <help><![CDATA[
  This element refers to the metadata point of contact.
  We place as default value the responsible for metadata about spatial datasets newly published 
  on the EEA website (Mauro who is working in SES2). This might be adjusted in future.<br/>
  ]]></help>
 </element>


 <element name="gmd:positionName" id="377.0">
  <label>Position name</label>
  <description>Role or position of the responsible person</description>
  <condition>conditional</condition>
  <helper>
   <option value="European air pollution data centre">European air pollution data centre</option>
   <option value="European biodiversity data centre">European biodiversity data centre</option>
   <option value="European climate change data centre">European climate change data centre</option>
   <option value="Environmental data centre for land use">Environmental data centre for land
    use</option>
   <option value="European water data centre">European water data centre</option>
   <option value="Other">Other</option>
  </helper>
 </element>


 <element name="gmd:maintenanceAndUpdateFrequency" id="143.0">
  <label>Maintenance and update frequency</label>
  <description>Frequency with which changes and additions are made to the resource after the
   initial resource is completed</description>
  <condition>mandatory</condition>
  <help>
   <![CDATA[This metadata element applies only to datasets with a revision number.
   In case no frequency from the list above is satisfactory, the following resourceMaintenance 
   metadata element should be used instead with the relevant frequency expressed as 
   PeriodDuration? (in this example, a frequency of 
   1 year and 6 months is expressed with P1Y6M0DT0H0M0S which stands for a period of 1Year and 6Months):]]>
  </help>
 </element>
 
 
 <element name="gmd:descriptiveKeywords" id="33.0">
  <label>Descriptive keywords</label>
  <description>Provides category keywords, their type, and reference source</description>
  <help>
   <![CDATA[
   <h2>INSPIRE Themes</h2>
   <ul>
   <li>There shall be one keyword/characterString element per Inspire spatial theme to 
   which the dataset belongs.</li>
   <li>Inspire spatial data themes should be assigned based on information contained 
   in tables 4A, 4B and 4C of Geospatial data requirements for spatial analysis, review 2009 
   (document available on request).</li>
   <li>Inspire spatial theme names shall be retrieved from the  English version of the GEMET 
   - Inspire themes list without any further editing (no change in capitalization etc.).</li>
   </ul>
   <h2>GEMET Concepts</h2>
   <ul>
     <li>There shall be one keyword/characterString element per GEMET concept to which 
     the dataset belongs.</li>
     <li>There should be at least 2-3 GEMET concepts per dataset.</li>
     <li>GEMET concept names shall be retrieved from the  
     <a href="http://www.eionet.europa.eu/gemet/index_html?langcode=en">English version of the GEMET - Concepts list</a> (sorted by themes) 
     without any further editing (no change in capitalization etc.).</li>
   </ul>
   <h2>EEA keywords</h2>
   <ul>
     <li>EEA keywords are intended to be used by search engines (i.e. facetted search on 
     EEA website, search functionality in Geonetwork through web and CSW interfaces)</li>
     <li>EEA keywords shall be short, meaningful and shall not duplicate other metadata 
     elements which can act as keywords too (i.e. spatialRepresentationType, 
     Inspire themes, EEA categories, topicCategory)</li>
     <li><a href="https://taskman.eionet.europa.eu/Help/wiki/catalogue/eea_keywords">Already existing keywords</a>
     should be reused.<li>
     <li>Where relevant, a keyword related to the spatial coverage shall be used: EU15, 
     EU10, EU25, EU27, EFTA4, EEA32</li>
   </ul>
   <h2>EEA data categories</h2>
   This metadata element is used to discriminate between geospatial datasets, maps, figures, charts, etc.
   We are currently reviewing only geospatial datasets with an explicit or implicit spatial component, 
   therefore this metadata element does not need to be edited.
   ]]>
  </help>
 </element>
 
 
 <element name="gmd:resourceConstraints" id="35.0">
  <label>Resource constraints</label>
  <description>Provides information about constraints which apply to the
   resource(s)</description>
  <help>
   <![CDATA[
   Datasets owned by EEA and which can be freely distributed (this is the default for EEA owned datasets).
   For datasets which are not owned by EEA but are distributed by EEA, contact Paul Hasenohr
   For datasets which are protected by intellectual property rights (typically datasets acquired
   from external providers like Gisco) set copyright and license for the legal constraints.
   ]]>
  </help>
 </element>
 
 
 <element name="gmd:scaleDenominator" id="94.0">
  <label>Scale Denominator</label>
  <description>Denominator of the representative fraction on a source map</description>
  <help>Although it is possible to specify several spatial resolutions, we require 
   to have only one (smallest scale or coarsest resolution).</help>
 </element>
 
 
 <element name="gmd:EX_GeographicBoundingBox" id="343.0">
  <label>Geographic bounding box</label>
  <description>Geographic position of the dataset</description>
  <help>
   <![CDATA[
   Coordinates are expressed in decimal degrees with positive east and north.
   When rounding up decimal values, make sure to do it in such a way 
   that the bounding box gets larger and not smaller:
   <ul>
     <li>westBoundLongitude = -33.90432 rounded up to two decimals becomes westBoundLongitude = -33.91</li>
     <li>westBoundLongitude = 3.4262 rounded up to two decimals becomes westBoundLongitude = 3.42</li>
     <li>eastBoundLongitude = 38.1471 rounded up to two decimals becomes eastBoundLongitude = 38.15</li>
     <li>eastBoundLongitude = -1.2156 rounded up to two decimals becomes eastBoundLongitude = -1.21</li>
     <li>same principle apply by analogy for north and south latitudes.</li>
   </ul>
   ]]>
  </help>
 </element>
 
 
 <element name="gmd:EX_TemporalExtent" id="350.0">
  <label>Temporal Extent</label>
  <description>Time period covered by the content of the dataset</description>
  <help>
   <![CDATA[
   This element describes the time period covered by the content of the dataset.
   The time coverage written in the default template does not correctly describe the dataset 
   (Corine Land Cover changes over 1990-2000), a more accurate description would use as:
   <ul>
     <li>starting date: date when first set of images and corresponding ground truth records have been acquired</li>
     <li>ending date: date when last set of images and corresponding ground truth records have been acquired</li>
   </ul>
   A full year should be expressed as starting on January, 1st and ending on December, 31st.<br/>
   In case a time should be specified in addition to a date, time should be expressed as GMT and the following format should 
   be used: 1977-03-10T11:45:30.<br/>
   For time series with today as end date, the indeterminatePosition attribute should be set to "now".
   ]]>
  </help>
 </element>
 
 <element name="gmd:name" context="gmd:MD_Format" id="285.0">
  <label>Name</label>
  <description>Name of the data transfer format(s)</description>
  <help>The format in which the resource is stored should be expressed 
   using a code from this list which is derived from the codes used 
   by the libraries GDAL and OGR (if a format is missing, contact Paul Hasenohr):
   We remind that use of unpublished formats should be avoided as much as possible 
   to ensure the best possible interoperability.</help>
  <condition>mandatory</condition>
  <helper rel="gmd:version">
   <option value="">-- Raster --</option>
   <option value="AAIGrid">Arc/Info ASCII Grid</option>
   <option value="AIG">Arc/Info Binary Grid (.adf)</option>
   <option value="CEOS">CEOS format (used by some satellite image providers)</option>
   <option value="DIMAP">DIMAP format (used by some satellite image providers)</option>
   <option value="ECW">ERMapper Compressed Wavelets (.ecw)</option>
   <option value="EHdr">ESRI .hdr Labelled</option>
   <option value="ENVI">ENVI .hdr Labelled Raster</option>
   <option value="GRASS">GRASS Rasters</option>
   <option value="GTiff" title="1.0">TIFF / BigTIFF / GeoTIFF (if no georeferencing information is available in the TIFF file itself, an ESRI world file [.tfw] must be present)</option>
   <option value="HDF">Hierarchical Data Format Release (specify the version number [4 or 5] in the metadata element version)</option>
   <option value="HFA">Erdas Imagine (.img)</option>
   <option value="LAN">Erdas 7.x .LAN and .GIS</option>
   <option value="MrSID">Multi-resolution Seamless Image Database</option>
   <option value="netCDF">NetCDF</option>
   <option value="XYZ">ASCII Gridded XYZ</option>
   
   <option value="">-- Vector --</option>
   <option value="AVCBin">Arc/Info Binary Coverage</option>
   <option value="AVCE00">Arc/Info .E00 (ASCII) Coverage</option>
   <option value="CSV">Comma Separated Value (.csv)</option>
   <option value="FGeo">ESRI File GeoDatabase</option>
   <option value="GML" title="3.1.1">Geography Markup Language</option>
   <option value="GRASS">GRASS vector</option>
   <option value="KML">Keyhole Markup Language</option>
   <option value="MIF" title="4.5">MapInfo File</option>
   <option value="PGeo">ESRI Personal GeoDatabase</option>
   <option value="SHP" title="1.0">ESRI Shapefile</option>
   <option value="Postgis">Postgresql/Postgis database</option>
   
   
  </helper>
 </element>
 
 
 <element name="gmd:transferOptions" id="273.0">
  <label>Transfer options</label>
  <description>Provides information about technical means and media by which a resource is
   obtained from the distributor</description>
  <help>
   If the dataset has already been published, the permalink to the resource on the EEA website
   shall be provided in the linkage element with WWW:LINK-1.0-http--link as related protocol.
   The filepath starting from gis_sdi to the file which needs to be opened in order to access
   the resource shall be provided in the linkage element with EEA:FILEPATH as related protocol.
  </help>
 </element>
 
 
 <element name="gmd:LI_Lineage" id="82.0">
  <label>Lineage</label>
  <description>Information about the events or source data used in constructing the data
   specified by the scope or lack of knowledge about lineage</description>
  <help>All relevant steps taken in order to create the datasets shall be described here (
   process history) while addressing version specificities where suitable.
   The overall quality of the dataset should be included as well in this metadata element.</help>
 </element>
</labels>
