<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2001-2016 Food and Agriculture Organization of the
  ~ United Nations (FAO-UN), United Nations World Food Programme (WFP)
  ~ and United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP)
  ~
  ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
  ~ the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of the License, or (at
  ~ your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
  ~ WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
  ~ General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~ along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
  ~ Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301, USA
  ~
  ~ Contact: Jeroen Ticheler - FAO - Viale delle Terme di Caracalla 2,
  ~ Rome - Italy. email: geonetwork@osgeo.org
  -->

<strings>
  <understandResource>Information about the dataset</understandResource>
  <relatedResources>Related services and linked data</relatedResources>
  <techInfo>Technical information</techInfo>
  <contactInfo>Contact information</contactInfo>
  <mdContactInfo>Metadata contact</mdContactInfo>
  <refDate>Reference date</refDate>
  <temporalRef>Temporal information</temporalRef>
  <constraintInfo>Access constraint information</constraintInfo>
  <xml_iso19139>Save this metadata as an ISO19139 XML file</xml_iso19139>
  <xml_iso19139Tooai_dc>Save this metadata as an OAI Dublin Core XML file</xml_iso19139Tooai_dc>

  <metadata-contact>Metadata contact</metadata-contact>
  <eea>EEA</eea>
  <eea-add-inspire-conformity>Add INSPIRE conformity</eea-add-inspire-conformity>
  <eea-identification>Identification of resource</eea-identification>
  <eea-hr>
    <hr/>
  </eea-hr>
  <eea-lineage>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          This element provides a  statement  on  process history  and the  overall  quality  of  the  spatial  data  set.  The process history may be described with the information on the source data used and the main transformation steps that took place in creating the current data set (or dataset series). This element should also address version specificities where suitable. It should also include a statement whether the data set has been validated or quality assured, whether it is the official version (if multiple versions exist), and whether it has legal validity.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </eea-lineage>

  <eea-title-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">The title should be self-explanatory and should not contain acronyms unless they are widely known. In any case, should an acronym be used in the title, it shall be made explicit in the abstract. For datasets with versions please <a href="https://taskman.eionet.europa.eu/projects/public-docs/wiki/Naming_conventions#2-Dataset-Title-convention" target="_blank">follow this convention</a></div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-title-help>

  <eea-date-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">Set at least the creation date for the dataset, and publication date if the dataset is published on the EEA website. There shall be not more than one date of creation and publication. Optionally, date of last revision can be added when relevant.</div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-date-help>
  <eea-conformity-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">This data quality element informs about the outcome of the evaluation of the data set against the INSPIRE regulation as regards interoperability of spatial datasets and services. By default, we set it to "Not evaluated".</div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-conformity-help>
  <eea-edition-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          The version and revision numbers of the dataset should be encoded in this element, separated by a point (VersionNumber.RevisionNumber)
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-edition-help>
  <eea-distributionFormat>Distribution format</eea-distributionFormat>
  <eea-distributionFormat-add>Add distribution format</eea-distributionFormat-add>
  <eea-abstract-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          This is a brief narrative summary of the content of the resource. The abstract provides a clear and concise statement that enables the reader to
          understand the content of the data  or service. Ideally it should also
          contain information about the coverage (linguistic transcriptions of the
          extent or location), main attributes, data sources, legal references and
          importance of the work. Acronyms should be written in full when first used.
          When the metadata refers to a revision of an already existing dataset, it is
          important to indicate as well the main changes on this new version.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </eea-abstract-help>
  <eea-identifier-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          The dataset identifier shall be unique and ideally meaningful, following
          <a href="https://taskman.eionet.europa.eu/projects/public-docs/wiki/Naming_conventions" target="_blank">this convention</a>.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-identifier-help>
  <eea-graphicOverview-add>Add an overview</eea-graphicOverview-add>
  <eea-classification>Classification and keywords</eea-classification>
  <eea-topic>Classification - ISO 19115 Topic categories</eea-topic>
  <eea-topic-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"></div>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          Choose at least one from this code list. This is a high-level classification scheme defined in Part D 2 of the <a href="http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/PDF/?uri=CELEX:32008R1205&amp;from=EN" target="_blank">INSPIRE Metadata Regulation 1205/2008/EC</a> and are derived directly from the topic categories defined in MD_TopicCategoryCode (B.5.27) of ISO 19115.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-topic-help>
  <eea-keyword-inspire>Keywords – INSPIRE theme</eea-keyword-inspire>
  <eea-keyword-gemet>Keywords – GEMET concepts</eea-keyword-gemet>
  <eea-keyword-cat>Keywords – EEA data categories</eea-keyword-cat>
  <eea-keyword-list>Keywords – EEA keywords list</eea-keyword-list>
  <eea-keyword-spatial>Keywords – Spatial coverage of the dataset</eea-keyword-spatial>

  <eea-inspire-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"></div>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          Choose at least one of the 34 INSPIRE Spatial Data Themes.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-inspire-help>

  <eea-gemet-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"></div>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          Choose at least 2-3 GEMET concepts.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-gemet-help>
  <eea-country-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"></div>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          This metadata element is used to describe the intended spatial coverage of a dataset in text form. Where appropriate, country codes such as those described <a href="https://taskman.eionet.europa.eu/projects/public-docs/wiki/Country_codes" target="_blank">here</a> should be used instead of listing all Member States.

        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-country-help>
  <eea-categories-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"></div>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          By default the EEA category is set to “geospatial data” as the SDI only publishes metadata of geospatial datasets for now. Should you need to add more keywords here please contact <a href="mailto:sdi@eea.europa.eu">the SDI Team</a>.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-categories-help>
  <eea-keywords-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"></div>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          EEA keywords shall be short, meaningful and shall not duplicate other metadata elements (such as INSPIRE Themes, GEMET or EEA categories). Whenever possible, keywords from <a href="https://taskman.eionet.europa.eu/projects/public-docs/wiki/Catalogueeea_keywords" target="_blank">the list of terms used in the EEA website</a> to tag datasets shall be reused.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-keywords-help>
  <eea-category>Catalogue category</eea-category>
  <eea-catalogcategory-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"></div>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          Select additional catalogue labels for your metadata. Should the dataset be free, full and open for re-use, please select the label geodatacore so this dataset can be discovered by the <a href="http://www.geoportal.org/" target="_blank">GEOSS</a>.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </eea-catalogcategory-help>

  <eea-coverage>Spatial and Temporal Extent</eea-coverage>
  <eea-add-extent>Add bounding box</eea-add-extent>
  <eea-add-temporal-extent>Add temporal extent</eea-add-temporal-extent>
  <eea-bbox-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
        This is the actual geographic extent of the resource, represented by the minimum rectangle which encompasses all features in the dataset. The  bounding  box  shall  be  expressed  in  decimal  degrees  with  a precision of at least 2 decimals, with positive east and north. For datasets including overseas territories, it is advised to split the overall geographic extent into several bounding boxes. The coordinates of the bounding boxes shall be expressed in any geodetic coordinate reference system with the Greenwich Prime Meridian.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-bbox-help>
  <eea-temporalresolution-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          ISO 19115-1 refers to this element as the smallest resolvable temporal period in a resource. <a href="https://link.springer.com/referenceworkentry/10.1007%2F978-0-387-35973-1_1376" target="_blank">Springer</a> defines temporal resolution as the amount of time needed to revisit and acquire data for the exact same location. When applied to remote sensing, this amount of time depends on the orbital characteristics of the sensor platform as well as sensor characteristics. This element is to be filled in in particular for time series.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </eea-temporalresolution-help>
  <eea-temporal-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          This element describes the time period covered by the content of the dataset, normally related to the data collection period. When the dataset refers to a (specific) full year, Begin Date should be set to 1st January of that year and End Date should be set to 31st December of that year.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </eea-temporal-help>

  <eea-add-temporal-resolution>Add temporal resolution</eea-add-temporal-resolution>

  <eea-maintenance-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          Frequency with which modifications and deletions are made to the data after it is first produced. This element takes a value out of the codelist of ISO19115 element MD_MaintenanceFrequencyCode). In case no frequency from the list is satisfactory, switch to the <a href="#/metadata/{{gnCurrentEdit.id}}?tab=identificationInfo">full view</a> and use the element PeriodDuration as indicated in the EEA metadata guidelines.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-maintenance-help>
  <eea-format-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          This elements provides the format(s) in which the resource is stored and distributed. The element should be expressed using codes from the list derived from those used by the libraries GDAL and OGR (if a format is missing, contact <a href="mailto:sdi@eea.europa.eu">the SDI Team</a>)
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </eea-format-help>

  <eea-additional>Additional technical information</eea-additional>
  <eea-contacts>Responsible Party</eea-contacts>
  <eea-contact-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          This element provides the identification of those organisations associated with the dataset. By default, and for EEA owned datasets, the responsible party for the roles of “point of contact” and “custodian” of the dataset is set to the EEA. If the dataset is not owned by the EEA, select a contact from the list of predefined entries. Contact <a href="mailto:sdi@eea.europa.eu">the SDI team</a> if you think a new contact should be added to the register.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </eea-contact-help>

  <eea-resourceConstraints>Resource Constraints</eea-resourceConstraints>
  <eea-resourceConstraints-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          This element provides a statement on any limitation that can affect the fitness of use of the resource or metadata.  The EEA template includes by default <a href="https://taskman.eionet.europa.eu/projects/public-docs/wiki/Cataloguemetadata_guidelines#MD_MetadataidentificationInforesourceConstraints" target="_blank">the standard text to be included for those datasets owned by EEA which can be freely distributed</a>. For datasets which are not owned by EEA but are distributed by EEA please insert the statement corresponding to the applicable policy. In case of a doubt please contact  <a href="mailto:sdi@eea.europa.eu">the SDI team</a>.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </eea-resourceConstraints-help>

  <eea-otherConstraints-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          Other restrictions and legal prerequisites for accessing and using the resource or metadata. For EEA datasets this element is set to “No limitations”.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-otherConstraints-help>


  <eea-accessConstraints-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          Code list based element which refers to any constraints applied to assure the protection of privacy or intellectual property and any special restriction or limitation on obtaining the resource or the metadata. By default and for EEA datasets this element is set to “Other Restrictions”. For datasets which are not owned by EEA but are distributed by EEA please select the appropriate code from the list. In case of a doubt please contact <a href="mailto:sdi@eea.europa.eu">the SDI team</a>.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-accessConstraints-help>


  <eea-crs-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          The Coordinate Reference System shall be referred to with its <a href="http://www.spatialreference.org/" target="_blank">EPSG code</a>, here we provide only those more commonly used at the EEA. Should you require any CRS not present in this list please contact <a href="mailto:sdi@eea.europa.eu">the SDI Team</a>.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-crs-help>

  <eea-spatialreptype-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          Method used to spatially represent geographic information, based on the elements of the codelist defined in ISO 19115 MD_SpatialRepresentationTypeCode.
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-spatialreptype-help>

  <eea-spatialresolution-help>
    <div class="row">
      <div class="col-sm-2"/>
      <div class="col-sm-10">
        <div class="alert alert-info">
          This element refers to the level of detail of the data set. It shall be expressed either as a resolution distance (typically for gridded data and imagery-derived products) or the equivalent scale (typically for maps or map-derived products), but not both. Although it is possible to specify several spatial resolutions, we require to have only one (smallest scale or coarsest resolution).
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
    <hr/>
  </eea-spatialresolution-help>

  <eea-associatedResource-help>
    <div class="alert alert-info">
      When available, please add the link to the web download using the Web address (URL) protocol, to the WMS GetCapabilities and corresponding layer using “OGC:WMS” protocol as well as the link to the ESRI Rest service using the “ESRI:REST” protocol. Links for internal access, the graphic overview and related data sources will be added by the SDI Team during the registration process.
    </div>
  </eea-associatedResource-help>
  <eea-technical-details>Spatial representation and resolution</eea-technical-details>
  <eea-dq>Data quality</eea-dq>
  <eea-constraints>Resource constraints</eea-constraints>

  <eea-contact>
    <div class="alert alert-info">
      <i class="fa fa-question-circle"></i>&#160; For more details about how to create EEA metadata please read the <a href="https://taskman.eionet.europa.eu/projects/public-docs/wiki/SDI_editor_guidance" target="_blank">EEA Metadata Guidelines</a>. Elements with a <label style="color: #a94442;font-size: 1em;">*</label> are mandatory with respect to the EEA metadata guidelines.
    </div>
    <div class="alert alert-info">
      If you have any questions, please contact <a href="mailto:sdi@eea.europa.eu">sdi [at] eea.europa.eu</a>.
    </div>
  </eea-contact>
  <addSpatialRepresentationType>Add spatial representation type (ie. grid, vector, text)</addSpatialRepresentationType>
  <addCrs>Choose a coordinate reference system</addCrs>
  <addCrs4326>WGS 84 (EPSG:4326)</addCrs4326>
  <addCrs4258>ETRS 89 (EPSG:4258)</addCrs4258>
  <addCrs3035>ETRS 89 / LAEA Europe  (EPSG:3035)</addCrs3035>
  <addCrs32628>WGS 84 / UTM zone 28N (EPSG:32628)</addCrs32628>
  <addCrs32629>WGS 84 / UTM zone 29N (EPSG:32629)</addCrs32629>
  <addCrs32630>WGS 84 / UTM zone 30N (EPSG:32630)</addCrs32630>
  <addCrs32631>WGS 84 / UTM zone 31N (EPSG:32631)</addCrs32631>
  <addCrs32632>WGS 84 / UTM zone 32N (EPSG:32632)</addCrs32632>
  <addCrs32633>WGS 84 / UTM zone 33N (EPSG:32633)</addCrs32633>
  <addCrs32634>WGS 84 / UTM zone 34N (EPSG:32634)</addCrs32634>
  <addCrs32635>WGS 84 / UTM zone 35N (EPSG:32635)</addCrs32635>
  <addCrs32740>WGS 84 / UTM zone 40S (EPSG:32740)</addCrs32740>

  <!-- New strings added for the AngularJS editor -->
  <!-- View and tabs -->
  <advanced>Full</advanced>
  <default>Simple</default>
  <simple>Simple</simple>
  <simple>Simple</simple>
  <inspire>INSPIRE</inspire>
  <inspire_sds>SDS</inspire_sds>

  <keywordFrom>Keywords - </keywordFrom>
  <resource>Resource</resource>
  <xml>XML</xml>
  <metadata>Metadata</metadata>
  <identificationInfo>Identification</identificationInfo>
  <distributionInfo>Distribution</distributionInfo>
  <dataQualityInfo>Quality</dataQualityInfo>
  <spatialRepresentationInfo>Spatial rep.</spatialRepresentationInfo>
  <referenceSystemInfo>Ref. system</referenceSystemInfo>
  <contentInfo>Content</contentInfo>
  <portrayalCatalogueInfo>Portrayal</portrayalCatalogueInfo>
  <metadataConstraints>Md. constraints</metadataConstraints>
  <metadataMaintenance>Md. maintenance</metadataMaintenance>
  <applicationSchemaInfo>Schema info</applicationSchemaInfo>
  <noThesaurusName>Keywords</noThesaurusName>
  <bboxesSection>Geographic coverage</bboxesSection>
  <overviews>Overviews</overviews>
  <metadataInXML>XML</metadataInXML>
  <providedBy>Provided by</providedBy>
  <shareOnSocialSite>Share on social sites</shareOnSocialSite>
  <viewMode>Views</viewMode>
  <linkToPortal>Access to the portal</linkToPortal>
  <linkToPortal-help>Read here the full details and access to the data.</linkToPortal-help>
  <citationProposal>Citation proposal</citationProposal>
  <citationProposal-help>This proposal was automatically generated, check if the metadata authors did not specified custom citation requirements.</citationProposal-help>
  <associatedResources>Associated resources</associatedResources>

  <!-- XSD error translation -->
  <invalidElement>Invalid content found at element </invalidElement>
  <onElementOf>One of the following elements </onElementOf>
  <isExpected> is expected.</isExpected>
  <isNotComplete> is not complete.</isNotComplete>
  <elementLocated> Parent element is </elementLocated>
  <missingElement>Missing element in </missingElement>
  <invalidValue>Invalid or missing value.</invalidValue>
  <notValidFor> is not a valid value for </notValidFor>
  <xsdErrorIs>XSD error is: </xsdErrorIs>
  <inElement> in element </inElement>
  <enum1>Value </enum1>
  <enum2> is not valid for the field </enum2>
  <enum3>Potential values are: </enum3>

  <!-- INSPIRE view labels and help -->
  <url>Online resource</url>
  <identifier>Resource identifier</identifier>
  <rsIdentifier>Projection</rsIdentifier>
  <referenceDate>Temporal information</referenceDate>
  <creationDate>Creation date</creationDate>
  <hierarchyLevel>Hierarchy level</hierarchyLevel>
  <publicationDate>Publication date</publicationDate>
  <revisionDate>Revision date</revisionDate>
  <temporalRangeSection>Temporal extent</temporalRangeSection>
  <beginPosition>Begin</beginPosition>
  <endPosition>End</endPosition>
  <conformity>Conformity</conformity>
  <conformity_title>Title</conformity_title>
  <conformity_date>Date</conformity_date>
  <explanation>Explanation</explanation>
  <pass>Conformity</pass>
  <indeterminatePosition>Indeterminate position</indeterminatePosition>
  <pointOfContact>Contact for the resource</pointOfContact>
  <metadataPointOfContact>Contact for the metadata</metadataPointOfContact>
  <organisationName>Organisation name</organisationName>
  <electronicMailAddress>Email</electronicMailAddress>
  <role>Role</role>
  <encoding>Encoding</encoding>
  <inspireTheme>INSPIRE themes</inspireTheme>
  <inspireThemeURI>INSPIRE themes</inspireThemeURI>
  <format>Format</format>
  <format_version>Version</format_version>
  <format_specification>Specification</format_specification>
  <lineage>Lineage</lineage>
  <spatialResolution>Spatial resolution (scale denominator)</spatialResolution>
  <spatialDistance>Spatial resolution (distance)</spatialDistance>
  <accessConstraints>Access constraints</accessConstraints>
  <useConstraints>Use constraints</useConstraints>
  <useLimitation>Use limitation</useLimitation>
  <add-resource-id>Compute resource identifier</add-resource-id>
  <add-resource-idHelp>Compose the resource identifier using the catalog URL and the metadata
    identifier (eg. http://www.organization.org/catalogue/5391bf69-44bc-4ea0-8cc0-6cf6c3bc81ae).
  </add-resource-idHelp>
  <add-extent-from-geokeywords>Compute extent from keyword</add-extent-from-geokeywords>
  <add-extent-from-geokeywordsHelp>Analyze each keyword of type place and add matching extent.
  </add-extent-from-geokeywordsHelp>
  <classificationSection>Classification of data and services</classificationSection>
  <temporalSection>Temporal reference</temporalSection>
  <restrictionsSection>Restrictions on access and use</restrictionsSection>
  <metadataSection>Metadata information</metadataSection>
  <responsibleOrganisationSection>Responsible organization (s)</responsibleOrganisationSection>
  <qualityAndValiditySection>Quality and validity</qualityAndValiditySection>
  <spatialRepresentationType>Spatial representation type</spatialRepresentationType>
  <topicCategory>Topic category code</topicCategory>
  <metadataLanguage>Metadata language</metadataLanguage>
  <inspireServiceTaxonomy>INSPIRE Service Taxonomy</inspireServiceTaxonomy>
  <otherConstraints>Other constraints</otherConstraints>
  <operatesOn>Coupled resource</operatesOn>
  <extent>Geographic bounding box</extent>
  <freeTextKeywords>Other keywords</freeTextKeywords>
  <resource_url>URL</resource_url>
  <resource_protocol>Protocol</resource_protocol>

  <!--<addCrs>Projection</addCrs>-->
  <addCrs4936>ETRS89-XYZ</addCrs4936>
  <addCrs4937>ETRS89-GRS80h</addCrs4937>
  <addCrs4258>ETRS89-GRS80</addCrs4258>
  <addCrs3035>ETRS89-LAEA</addCrs3035>
  <addCrs3034>ETRS89-LCC</addCrs3034>
  <addCrs3038>ETRS89-TM26N</addCrs3038>
  <addCrs3039>ETRS89-TM27N</addCrs3039>
  <addCrs3040>ETRS89-TM28N</addCrs3040>
  <addCrs3041>ETRS89-TM29N</addCrs3041>
  <addCrs3042>ETRS89-TM30N</addCrs3042>
  <addCrs3043>ETRS89-TM31N</addCrs3043>
  <addCrs3044>ETRS89-TM32N</addCrs3044>
  <addCrs3045>ETRS89-TM33N</addCrs3045>
  <addCrs3046>ETRS89-TM34N</addCrs3046>
  <addCrs3047>ETRS89-TM35N</addCrs3047>
  <addCrs3048>ETRS89-TM36N</addCrs3048>
  <addCrs3049>ETRS89-TM37N</addCrs3049>
  <addCrs3050>ETRS89-TM38N</addCrs3050>
  <addCrs3051>ETRS89-TM39N</addCrs3051>
  <addCrs5730>EVRS</addCrs5730>
  <addCrs7409>ETRS89-GRS80-EVRS</addCrs7409>

  <!-- String for INSPIRE SDS tab -->

  <inspire_sds_cc1>Conformance class 1: invocable</inspire_sds_cc1>
  <inspire_sds_cc2>Conformance class 2: interoperable</inspire_sds_cc2>
  <inspire_sds_cc3>Conformance class 3: harmonized</inspire_sds_cc3>

  <sds-category>Category</sds-category>
  <inspire_add_pass>Add pass element</inspire_add_pass>
  <sds-add-dataquality>Add DataQuality element</sds-add-dataquality>
  <sds-add-dataqualityHelp>TG4: For each spatial data service, there shall be one and only one set
    of quality information (dataQualityInfo element) scoped to “service”.
  </sds-add-dataqualityHelp>
  <sds-add-tech-spec>Add a technical specification</sds-add-tech-spec>
  <sds-add-tech-specHelp>TG8: The Specification metadata element shall at least refer to or contain
    one technical specification to which the invocable spatial data service fully conforms,
    providing all the necessary technical elements, to actually invoke the service and enable its
    usage.
  </sds-add-tech-specHelp>
  <sds-tech-spec>Technical specification</sds-tech-spec>
  <conformity_desc>Tech spec title</conformity_desc>
  <conformity_linkage>Tech spec URL</conformity_linkage>


  <sds-section-qos>Quality of Service</sds-section-qos>
  <sds-add-qualityofservice>Add missing Quality of Service criteria</sds-add-qualityofservice>
  <sds-add-qualityofserviceHelp>INSPIRE SDS requires three quality of service criteria to be
    reported in the metadata: Availability, Performance and Capacity. This button will add the
    missing criteria.
  </sds-add-qualityofserviceHelp>
  <qos_measure>Measure:</qos_measure>
  <qos_uom>UOM</qos_uom>
  <qos_description>Description</qos_description>
  <qos_value>Value</qos_value>
  <sds-section-crs>Coordinate reference system</sds-section-crs>

  <sds-fix-category>Fix the Category element</sds-fix-category>
  <sds-fix-categoryHelp>(Rec1) Replace gco:CharacterString with gmx:Anchor in the description
    metadata element.
  </sds-fix-categoryHelp>

  <sds-accesspoint>Access Point URL</sds-accesspoint>
  <sds-add-accesspoint>Add Access Point</sds-add-accesspoint>

  <sds-endpoint>Endpoint URL</sds-endpoint>
  <sds-add-endpoint>Add Endpoint</sds-add-endpoint>

  <sds-addNoConstraints>No Limitation</sds-addNoConstraints>
  <sds-addNoConstraintsHelp>Add an element that documents that there are no limitation for this
    service.
  </sds-addNoConstraintsHelp>
  <sds-addUnknownConstraints>Unknown Limitation</sds-addUnknownConstraints>
  <sds-addConstraints>Customizable constraints</sds-addConstraints>

  <sds>
    <noConditionsApply>No conditions apply</noConditionsApply>
    <conditionsUnknown>Conditions unknown</conditionsUnknown>
  </sds>

  <sds-limitation>Limitation</sds-limitation>

  <sds-section-custodian>Responsible custodian</sds-section-custodian>
  <sds-addOperation>Add Operation</sds-addOperation>
</strings>
